{
    "id": "69c2b1b5c26c4578b9bca64b487dfc17",
    "title": "Gap Fills Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "We have lived here ........................................ 10 years.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "since"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He was accused ............................................. stealing.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "We .......................................... the work yesterday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "finished",
                "have finished"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "You won’t get well unless you ......................................... your medicine.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "take",
                "are taking"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He has been living in this house ...................................... five years.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "since",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "We .............................................. English for the last seven years.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "are learning",
                "learns",
                "have been learning"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Yesterday ........................................... a holiday, he went to see a film.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was",
                "being"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The new headmaster wants a house to ..........................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "live",
                "live in",
                "live at"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I ................................................ for you since 9 o’clock in the morning.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "am waiting",
                "waited",
                "have been waiting"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I ........................................ all the books to the library yesterday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "returned",
                "have returned",
                "has returned"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}